March 1st, 18 years ago.
On my way home, I saw Kaio standing alone in the park.
I guess it was a little before 6.
That night, I was on my way to the hideout.
I think it was to try and find my gloves.
But I don't remember if I found him there or not.
After I left, I saw Yuki sitting by himself on the bank, looking out at the river.
On the way back home, I took a shortcut that took me by the park again.
But this time when I looked in, Kaio was gone.
A week from now, Kaio will be the first victim in a series of kidnappings and murders.
Day X.
If I can get her to survive March 1st and spend the second with me at my birthday party,
that should be enough to change her future.
I'm not gonna let her die.
Day X.
Day X  Duong Rats
Day X
君を待った。 проводいたけれど。
過ぎれない明日も過ぎた。
立ち止まって。怒 write.
止めドない今日を嘆き合った。
記憶だって!永久には待ってて。
残らないものとtight意識して。
僕はず〜っとかきむしって。
心隅っこで泣いだ。
そしてどうか。
失くさないでよって 後悔した過ぎる日々を 後悔したんだよって そう言い逃した もうきっと
君を待った 僕は待った 途切れない明日も過ぎてって 僕は今日もかきむしって 忘れない傷をつけてるんだよ
僕は 君じゃないのさ
僕は 君を待った
君を待った
早い說ンガバーヒー
食べ急 Borning
energies acapeาか
オ 1950のお手のもの
エアニ additions
それがラッケット
共理土地の伟助
本当に例え
うちがあります
しぇって作って取り出しました
real? It is a date, isn't it? Mm-hmm. Then bring her by. I'd love to meet her. We can have hot pot
or something. Actually, I invited Kaio to the party. Oh. Kaio from a few streets over, huh? Damn,
she's good at getting info out of people. You can go. Just be safe. Thanks, Mom. Hurry up and
finish your breakfast, kiddo. Mm-hmm. Stand. Bow. Bye. Live man's gonna be home. Cool, huh?
What's a foul? What a bird, duh. You're so smart. This Saturday, Kaio's not staying home. I'm gonna
take her away from her mom and the beatings. Mr. Yashiro? Um, sir? What's up, guys? Can you
explain this? I don't get it. Sure. Oh, that's a tough one. What a bunch of flirty little
tramps. Ugh. What are you talking about? It's not like you never did that too, you know?
Instead of dissing him, go up there and show him who's boss. What's diss mean? You're trying
to sound cool? Gotta watch what I say. The teacher doesn't care about me anymore. He thinks
I'm a thief. I bet you do too. Not that I care. Hey, guys. I got an idea. Oh, yeah? What is it?
Um, let's go to the Science Center on Saturday. I'll ask Kaio to go too. Yeah, that's a great idea.
I can't make it. Sorry, but I've already made plans that day. Oh, really? Uh, same for me too,
dude. I, uh, got some important things need doing. Yeah, what he said. I'd like to go,
but I can't either. Sorry. Yeah, me too. Oh. It's better if it's just you and Kaio anyway. See ya.
Satoru, everything okay? Oh, yeah. I told him I couldn't hang out Saturday because I had a date
with you. What a lie. I did it again. But, uh, my mom wants me to get home early Saturday,
so... I just want to take you someplace cool. I'll ask her and get permission.
Kenya, could I see you in the faculty office for a sec? No way. You kids are too young to go out
on a date. But it's more like a field trip. We'll be learning stuff. You can stay home and learn
stuff. Besides, Kaio helps me around the house Saturdays. Oh, yeah? With what? Blown off steam?
You're right, Hook. Well, smartass. I don't have to tell you a damn thing. I just want to know why
you don't want Kaio to go with me. I got a zillion reasons why. First, you guys are too young to be
dating. Second, who's responsible if something happens? You? Don't even go there with me,
bitch. What's your problem? What do you get out of taking her anywhere? She's just a gloomy little
girl. I'm not getting anything. All I want is to keep her safe. Safe, huh? What do you think
you're keeping her safe from? You her knight in shining armor? God damn it. Now she knows I know
she beats on her. What do you want to do, Kaio? You want to go out with him?
You're not going anywhere, you slut! Mom! Watch it, Miss Hinazuki. You shouldn't say nasty
things like that about your daughter. Miss Fujinuma, I... This isn't any of your business.
Actually, half of this is my business. A trip to the science center can be very educational
for a kid. Don't you think we should encourage that? We are their parents. I'm a single mom,
too, so I know how tough it can get. Come by sometime and we'll talk.
Kaio, get inside.
Okay. So, Saturday? I'll see you then.
Did I screw everything up?
No. You were great.
Guess it's lucky I showed up when I did. I got off work early and saw you so naturally
I had to follow you.
What do you mean naturally?
Oh, nothing. Just kidding is all.
Anyway, you don't have to worry about Kaio tonight.
Did you notice how nice her clothes were?
Her mom goes to a lot of trouble to make her look presentable.
Do you know what's going on over there?
I didn't, but after what I just heard and saw, I have my suspicions.
My mom wasn't a reporter for nothing.
Kaio's a cutie, isn't she?
Dude, you're 29.
Hang in there, kiddo. For her.
I will.
It's Saturday, February the 27th.
It's sunny and clear.
And for the last couple days, Kaio's mom hasn't beaten her up.
Just like my mom said.
Look it! He's my friend.
You're an idiot.
Isn't this place the coolest? I love it!
I think we're the only ones here.
When it's quiet like this, I pretend I snuck in.
Then, if someone comes, I hide from them!
Hmph.
She didn't call me an idiot.
Take a look inside this thing.
You want to check out the next show in the planetarium?
We already saw enough stars on the mountain.
Yeah, I guess.
Hey, I have to use the bathroom.
Okay. I'll be here.
What the heck was that feeling back there?
It was like...
Deja vu.
I remember coming here a lot.
But this is my first time with Kaio.
I'm back.
Satoru.
Thanks for inviting me to come today.
Did you know that I'd like to come here too?
Wait...
Did I?
Is that why I chose it?
Or...
Or is this someplace special for you?
Because, like, you want to make manga and stuff.
We talked about the same thing 18 years ago.
Now I remember.
I came here by myself and ran into Kaio.
What's wrong?
Oh, uh...
Maybe?
Am I just repeating things?
Have I been doing it unconsciously this whole time and...
Not changing the future at all?
Hey, Kaio.
Let me carry that.
Okay.
But there's so much that has changed because of what I did different.
I can change the future.
I can.
Satoru.
I'm glad I had the guts to come today.
Mm-hmm.
Hey, guys.
Hi, Kaio.
What's up?
I finished the stuff I had to do early.
Sorry we got here so late.
There.
It changed.
Is it okay we came?
Yeah, of course it is.
Right, Kaio?
Mm-hmm.
Hey, wanna hold our coats too?
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
Thanks, Satoru.
Good morning.
Oh, hey, Kaio.
Morning.
Yes.
She's here on time on a Monday.
Damn.
You're pretty.
Oh, my God.
Satoru is so bad!
We gotta get engaged first, you lame brain.
Let's get engaged.
Congrats, you guys.
Settle down.
Let's do some learning today.
Tomorrow's the day Kaio disappears.
March 1st.
The moment of truth.
Later, Hiromi.
Yep, see you tomorrow.
Hey, Kaio.
Want to walk to school together?
I could swing by your place.
Okay.
Mom.
Hello.
I'll come and get you tomorrow morning.
Bye!
See you later, Mom!
Okay.
I left the house a little early.
It's March 1st, 1988.
Kaio was kidnapped 18 years ago today.
It's me, Kaio.
But things are different now.
Good morning, Satoru.
Good morning!
No one's going to hurt her.
Bye, Miss Hinazuki.
A lot of things have changed between this time 18 years ago and now.
You're holding hands on the park.
You're holding hands on everything now.
Kaio was targeted because she was always alone at the park.
But she's not alone anymore.
You guys are all still coming over tomorrow night, right?
Yeah.
Of course.
Yep.
She's had friends to hang out with the past few days.
I know.
Wanna go play a game?
And today, she's with me.
I kind of wanted to get home early today.
Come on, don't be like that.
We'll have fun.
Okay.
It'll be fine.
Looks like I won again.
You're good.
This sucks.
Satoru, I should be getting home.
Yeah, it's getting late.
It's getting late.
It's snowing.
I'll come by tomorrow, too.
See you in the morning.
Bye.
I said it loud like that on purpose.
That way, everyone heard me.
Kaio, her mom,
and anyone else who might be out there.
They know I'm here now.
Day X is almost over.
It's too good to be true.
I'm such a dumbass.
Like this is gonna change anything.
I did it.
The day's over.
I changed history.
Good morning, Mom.
What the?
It's not even six.
I know.
Bye.
What about breakfast?
I couldn't sleep after I got home.
I wanted to see Kaio again,
no matter how early it was.
morning, sleep well?
You're an idiot.
Are you guys still on for tonight?
Yeah, dude.
You know it.
If there's one thing I like more than cake,
it's birthday cake.
Cool.
You guys want to hit the market with me?
Hey, Satoru, Kaio,
I need your help putting these boxes away.
Huh?
Can't it wait till tomorrow?
It sort of figures.
We blew off the last time we had cleaning duties.
I guess.
Man, this is heavy.
Some friends they turned out to be.
Those doofuses totally bailed on us.
That'll be 5,000 yen, please.
Okay.
Wait a sec.
It cost 5,000 back then, too.
I remember I was so stoked about it being my birthday.
I spent all I had.
We made a ton of sandwiches,
but since it was just my mom and me,
we had a lot left over.
I'm home!
Ready, and...
Kaio!
Satoru!
Happy birthday, guys!
Wait.
Mom, you knew about this?
I helped out a little,
but they're the real masterminds behind this evil scheme.
So then today,
those chores were planned, too?
Uh-huh.
We asked Mr. Yoshiro to stall you.
He also told us it was Kaio's birthday today.
I guess our little surprise worked, huh?
Uh, yeah.
Guess what, Kaio?
Satoru insisted on getting a cake just for you.
I'm sorry, Satoru.
I tried,
but I couldn't finish your present in time.
Seriously?
You were making me something?
Mm-hmm.
That's why she wanted to get home early yesterday.
Last night,
I fell asleep before I could finish it.
That's okay.
You can give it to me later.
Hey, guys!
Let's make 5,000 yen worth of sandwiches!
Yeah!
What?
You spent all the money!
We all had a blast making those sandwiches together.
But this time,
there weren't any left over at the end of the night.
Friends are the best,
no doubt.
Everyone brought presents for Kaio and me.
Talk about a haul.
And then...
That's for me!
Thank you, Satoru.
Thank you, everyone.
You can leave the cleaning up to us.
Yeah, walk Kaio home.
It's so cold!
You're an idiot.
Good night!
Here.
Thank you for today.
I'm glad I got to be friends with you and the others.
I'll give you your present tomorrow.
Promise.
Can't wait.
Good night.
I did it.
It worked.
I changed history.
Everyone had left by the time I got home.
I was so exhausted from the past few days,
all that built-up tension finally popped.
I collapsed on my futon and slept like a log.
Son of a bitch!
I'm late!
I'm here, sir!
Sorry!
Just in time.
I was about to mark you tardy.
Made it.
Okay.
Does anyone know if Kaio's coming today?
Kaio didn't show up that day.
Or the next one.
And that promise she made me,
she never got to keep it.
She never got to keep it.
I was stuck with the air in my heart
The air now full of insecurity
I still needtie
Butter with children
You shall tend to grow
But always growing up
It is something that I put in
The pure Dassault
Say it in front of you
I have something that I talk to you
Cause I show you
I'll be meeting you
But once more
Coming in
This世界
Will you live
With you
I would not like to
whether that student
Acadote
I won't leave
You